Donald and Charlotte MacJannet Papers MS024
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs and other media, 1880 -- 2000; 1915 -- 1999; MS024.007; 34.95 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 58 Audiovisual Object(s); 727 Digital Object(s)
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1924-05; MS024.007.DO.03489; Steueberg, K.E. (Box Shared 33)
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet posing with a group of people, 1925; MS024.007.DO.03490; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Charlotte is kneeling in front, on the far left (looking at the photo),
    Otto Blensdorf is older gentleman with the moustache on the right.
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; Blensdorf, Otto
  - Relatives of Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1936; MS024.007.DO.03491; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    the nephew and niece (probably) of Charlotte Blensdorf
    MacJannet
    People; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print
  - Granger Benson and Peter Tompkins playing at camp, 1926; MS024.007.DO.03492; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    People; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Benson, Granger; Tompkins, Peter; MacJannet Camp
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1923-05; MS024.007.DO.03493; Steueberg, K.E. (Box Shared 33)
  - Charlotte MacJannet and a companion, presumably Jean MacJannet Foster, 1960; MS024.007.DO.03494; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; Foster, Jean MacJannet
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet in Talloires, 1950-06-19; MS024.007.DO.03495; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
  - Charlotte MacJannet with a group of unidentified people, 1960; MS024.007.DO.03496; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
  - Donald and Charlotte MacJannet at thier home in Geneva, 1960; MS024.007.DO.03497; Martin, Francois (Box Shared 33)
  - Gerda Alexander, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03498; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print
  - Morning exercises at The Elms, 1938; MS024.007.DO.03567; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Students; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - A woman in costume visiting the MacJannet Camp, 1938; MS024.007.DO.03568; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    negative is attached to UI03569 - total size of both negatives is 2x6
    People; Costumes; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; MacJannet Camp
  - A meal at the MacJannet Camp, 1938; MS024.007.DO.03569; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    negative is attached to UI03568 - total size of both negatives is 2x6
    People; Children; Dinners and Dining; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; MacJannet Camp
  - Babe Ruth at the MacJannet School, 1935-02; MS024.007.DO.03581; Unknown (Box Shared 119)
    8x10
    People; Students; Baseball; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Ruth, Babe; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Donald and Charlotte MacJannet photographed with other Tufts alums, 1980; MS024.007.DO.03582; Hartnett, June M. (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    (top row): Donald MacJannet, Arthur Donnellan, Francis Curtin, Phillip Evans, Charlotte MacJannet, Rose Valentine, Marc Valentine, Helen Sampson Moore, Edward Gore. (second row): Mabel Donnes Watson, Helen Sibley Goodspeed, Mrs. Austin L. Baker (Aya), Gladys Day Black, Mrs. Edward Gore (Thelma). (lower row): Miss Nancy Robertson, Margaret O'Brien Piggott, Daniel O'Brien, Austin L. Baker, Jr., Dorothy Chase Reed.
  - Emory and Jean MacJannet Foster dressed for the opera, 1937-06; MS024.007.DO.03583; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    3x6
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Emory; Foster, Jean MacJannet
  - Jean MacJannet Foster enjoying a swim and sun-bathing at camp, 1927; MS024.007.DO.03584; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    5x7
    People; Staff; Swimming; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet School winter holiday skiing trip, 1927; MS024.007.DO.03585; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Students; Children; Skiing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School; MacJannet Camp
  - Jean MacJannet during a MacJannet School trip to North Africa, 1927; MS024.007.DO.03586; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    2x4
    People; Faculty; Students; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Jean MacJannet Foster with a student, summer, 1927; MS024.007.DO.03587; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    2x3
    People; Faculty; Students; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet School
  - Jean MacJannet Foster and Josephine MacJannet Upton with an unidentified woman, 1915; MS024.007.DO.03588; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    unidentified woman believed to be the mother or grandmother of Donald, Josephine, Malcolm and Jean MacJannet
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet; Upton, Josephine MacJannet
  - Otto Blensdorf, 1941; MS024.007.DO.03589; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    2x2
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Blensdorf, Otto
  - Emory and Jean MacJannet enjoying tea or coffee with an unidentified man, 1935; MS024.007.DO.03590; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Jean MacJannet Foster and Josephine MacJannet Upton, 1915; MS024.007.DO.03591; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    3.5x6
  - Jean MacJannet Foster, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03592; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
  - Jean MacJannet Foster and Donald MacJannet with the Rector of the University of Lausanne and his wife at the 400th anniversary celebration of the University of Lille, 1964; MS024.007.DO.03593; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet, Donald Ross
  - Children at the MacJannet Camp, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03599; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    2x1
  - Jean MacJannet Foster en route to Algeria, 1927; MS024.007.DO.03600; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Faculty; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet School
  - Campers lining-up at the MacJannet Camp, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03601; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    5
  - Students of the MacJannet School photographed in the snow, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03602; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Students; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School
  - A group photo while snow skiing, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03603; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    assumed that the group is part of a MacJannet winter holiday ski trip
    People; Faculty; Staff; Students; Children; Skiing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School
  - Diving off a platform at the MacJannet Camp, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03604; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    3x5
  - Woody Woodworth doing on a handstand on a column at the old roman ruins in Timgad, Algeria, 1927-04; MS024.007.DO.03605; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    3.5x7
    People; Faculty; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Woodworth, Lynn "Woody"; MacJannet School
  - An Egyptian fantasy, a theatrical production performed by MacJannet campers, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03606; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    photo is attached to an 8x10 piece of paper
    People; Children; Theater; Pageants; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
  - Lake Dwellers Pageant: an Attack Repelled, a theatrical production performed by MacJannet campers, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03607; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
  - Woody and Anita Woodworth and an unidentified couple with a castle in the background, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03608; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    4x6
    People; Buildings; Castles; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Woodworth, Lynn "Woody"; Woodworth, Anita
  - Campers walk past the lodge to the MacJannet school bus, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03609; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    photo is attached to 8x10 piece of paper
    People; Children; Buildings; Lodges; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
  - Football practice at the MacJannet Camp on Lake Annecy, 1927; MS024.007.DO.03610; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    Views; People; Children; Football; Tents; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
  - The Talloires peninsula jutting out into Lake Annecy, 1927; MS024.007.DO.03611; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    Views; Lakes; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print
  - Elms School pupils and their parents at the Pont du Gard acqueduct near Nimes, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03612; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Students; Views; Monuments; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Campers swimming in Lake Annecy under the watchful eye of a lifeguard, 1925; MS024.007.DO.03613; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Seventeen nationalities are represented at the daily flag salute at camp, 1925; MS024.007.DO.03614; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - French war orphans grew in skills, weight and health in yearly groups at the MacJannet summer camps, 1945; MS024.007.DO.03615; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    3.5x9
    People; Children; World War, 1939-1945; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet Camp
  - Jean MacJannet Foster and Donald MacJannet, 1980; MS024.007.DO.03616; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    3x3
  - Jean MacJannet Foster and Malcolm and Donald MacJannet, 1980; MS024.007.DO.03617; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet, Malcolm; MacJannet, Donald Ross
  - Campers brushing their teeth by the banks of Lake Annecy, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03618; Gouville, M. (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
  - Campers in canoes, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03619; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Children; Canoes and canoeing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; MacJannet Camp
  - Campers saluting the American flag, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03620; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Children; Flags; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; MacJannet Camp
  - MacJannet Camp staff member, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03621; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Staff; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; MacJannet Camp
  - Campers having a laugh while sitting in front of a fireplace, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03622; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Campers standing at attention beside the flag pole, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03623; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Staff; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; MacJannet Camp
  - Jean MacJannet Foster snow skiing, 1939; MS024.007.DO.03624; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    2x5
    People; Skiing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1922; MS024.007.DO.03625; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Students at the MacJannet School, 1925; MS024.007.DO.03626; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - The Elms School, 1925; MS024.007.DO.03627; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    Buildings; Schools; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Jean MacJannet Foster in Biarritz, 1955; MS024.007.DO.03628; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Donald MacJannet and others in costume, 1925; MS024.007.DO.03629; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Theater; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; MacJannet, Donald Ross
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet and Jean MacJannet Foster in Germany, 1964; MS024.007.DO.03630; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Phyllis Heathcote (foreground) and Jean MacJannet Foster at Font Romeu, 1937 -- 1938; MS024.007.DO.03631; New York times (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Heathcote, Phyllis; Foster, Jean MacJannet
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet posing for the camera with other performers, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03632; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, Malcolm MacJannet, and Jean MacJannet Foster, 1960; MS024.007.DO.03633; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Malcolm; Foster, Jean MacJannet
  - Jean MacJannet Foster at approximately seven years old in Boston, 1915; MS024.007.DO.03634; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet
  - Donald MacJannet in uniform, 1917; MS024.007.DO.03635; Orren Jack Turner Co. (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    People; World War, 1914-1918; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Donald Ross
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1990; MS024.007.DO.03636; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Diving at camp, 1935; MS024.007.DO.03637; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Amelia Earhart signing an autograph for Emory Foster while Donald MacJannet looks on during a visit to the MacJannet School, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03638; Associated Press of Great Britain, Ltd. (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    People; Staff; Students; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Earhart, Amelia; Foster, Emory; MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Students at the MacJannet School, 1925; MS024.007.DO.03639; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    6x8
  - Group photograph of a MacJannet winter ski trip with Jean and Emory Foster standing in the center, 1935; MS024.007.DO.03640; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Staff; Students; Children; Skiing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Emory; Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet School
  - Prince Philip of Greece and Denmark (blond boy in the center of the photograph) surrouded by his MacJannet school mates, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03641; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
  - Monsieur J. Boyer, President of the Banque de Paris et Pays Bas, saluting MacJannet campers Yvaine, Georges, and Claud Boyer, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03642; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    7x7
    People; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Boyer, J.; Boyer, Claud; Boyer, Georges; Boyer, Yvaine; MacJannet Camp; Banque de Paris; Banque de Pays Bas
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1988-11; MS024.007.DO.03643; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Jacques de Felice, the first French MacJannet camper, 1988; MS024.007.DO.03644; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; de Felice, Jacques; MacJannet Camp
  - Dress-up with MacJannet School students and faculty, possibly during a ski trip, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03645; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    Jean and Emory Foster (back row, 4th and 5th from the right)
    People; Faculty; Students; Costumes; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Emory; Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet School
  - The MacJannet home in Arlington (Mass.), 1944; MS024.007.DO.03646; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    photo taken from MS024/001-011
    Buildings; Houses; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print
  - View of the MacJannet home in Arlington from the backyard, 1944; MS024.007.DO.03647; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
  - Students at the Elms School in St. Cloud, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03648; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    People; Students; Buildings; Schools; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - MacJannet School students with Prince Philip in the middle, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03649; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
    photo attached to an 8x10 piece of paper
  - Woody Woodworth giving a lesson in water rescue techniques, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03650; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    photo is an irregular shape
    People; Staff; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Woodworth, Lynn "Woody"; MacJannet Camp
  - Students at the Elms School in St. Cloud, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03651; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Students of the Elms School in St. Cloud, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03652; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Donald MacJannet and his "protege," Paul Sawada, standing at the site where they stood thrity-five years ago, 1968-11; MS024.007.DO.03653; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Donald Ross; Sawada, Paul; MacJannet Camp
  - Students in costume at the MacJannet School, 1925; MS024.007.DO.03654; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Students; Costumes; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - MacJannet students in costume, 1925; MS024.007.DO.03655; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_1d568d60c03ef854e689afaf1955b3aa)
  - Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, 1935; MS024.007.DO.03656; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - An outdoor theatrical production at the MacJannet School, 1935; MS024.007.DO.03657; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Students; Theater; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - MacJannet students riding on a camel during a field trip to a zoo, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03658; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Students; Camels; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Stage backdrop for MacJannet student theatrical perfomances, 1935; MS024.007.DO.03659; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    Theater; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Female students at the Elms School in St. Cloud, 1935; MS024.007.DO.03660; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Students at the Elms School in St. Cloud, 1935; MS024.007.DO.03661; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Jean MacJannet Foster wiping the chin of a young boy, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03662; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Staff; Students; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - Ice skaters during a MacJannet winter ski trip, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03663; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Students; Children; Skating; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - MacJannet students in costume, 1928; MS024.007.DO.03664; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Jean MacJannet Foster and a driver with students during an Elms School day trip, 1925; MS024.007.DO.03665; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Staff; Students; Cathedrals; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet School (The Elms)
  - MacJannet School athletic team, 1930; MS024.007.DO.03666; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Charlotte and Donald MacJannet in Bethlehem, 1938; MS024.007.DO.03685; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    taken from MS027/007-094
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1938; MS024.007.DO.03686; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    taken from MS024/007-094
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet and Jean MacJannet Foster having tea with ladies of the Blensdorf family, 1938; MS024.007.DO.03687; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
  - Donald and Charlotte MacJannet with four unidentified people, 1976; MS024.007.DO.03688; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    taken from MS027/007-014 - "Scrapbook of the Priory and visitors, ca. 1976"
  - Donald MacJannet with visitors standing before the Priory in Talloires, 1976; MS024.007.DO.03689; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    taken from MS024/007-014 - "Scrapbook of the Priory and visitors, ca. 1976"
    People; Priories; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Donald Ross
  - Sherry Walters-Stephens and David Walters at Talloires, 1976; MS024.007.DO.03690; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; Walters-Stephens, Sherry; Walters, David
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1976; MS024.007.DO.03691; Odesser Annecy (Box data_value_missing_04dbc24a9d579b322123f851192894b4)
  - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet at the Priory in Talloires, 1976; MS024.007.DO.03692; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_bd683c5ae1765268794d8c40545ff3ad)
    People; Priories; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; photographic print; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf